Every mission has its demons.
Shadow in the Cloud is a horror, action, war film directed by Roseanne Liang.
A WWII pilot traveling with top secret documents on a B-17 Flying
Fortress encounters an evil presence on board the flight.
Maude Garrett, played by Chloë Grace Moretz.
Stu Beckell, played by Nick Robinson.
Anton Williams, played by Beulah Koale.
Walter Quaid, played by Taylor John Smith.
John Reeves, played by Callan Mulvey.
Tommy Dorn, played by Benedict Wall.
Shadow in the Cloud is a 2020 action horror film directed by Roseanne Liang, from a screenplay by Liang and Max
Landis, starring Chloë Grace Moretz, Beulah Koale, Taylor John Smith, Callan Mulvey and Nick Robinson.
It follows a female flight officer on a top-secret mission in the Pacific during the Second World War, who
after boarding a Boeing B-17 Flying Fortress, encounters an evil gremlin during the flight.
The film was an international co-production between New Zealand and United States, The film premiered on September 12, 2020,
at the 2020 Toronto International Film Festival, where it won the People's Choice Award for Midnight Madness.
It was released on January 1, 2021, by Vertical
Entertainment and Redbox Entertainment.
The film explores themes of world war ii, gremlin, top
secret, female pilot, woman director.
The tone is dark.